<_>
   <form_key>T4nWNkYfrMPqx0Y0</form_key>
   <name>Diglin_Username</name>
   <channel>community</channel>
   <version_ids>
      <version_ids>2</version_ids>
   </version_ids>
   <summary>Create and login to an account thanks to a username AND email address.&amp;#xD;
Allow to disable an account from backend. The user will be blocked if the option in the customer backend is set to no</summary>
   <description>This module allows you to:&amp;#xD;
&amp;#xD;
- login with a username or email address. it can be done from frontend during checkout or getting access to the customer account&amp;#xD;
- Username can have letters, digits, &apos;_-&apos; but no other special characters&amp;#xD;
- Username length is from 6 until 30 characters possible&amp;#xD;
- save a username from frontend (register account or checkout process) or from backend by editing a customer account&amp;#xD;
- check that the username doesn&apos;t already exists&amp;#xD;
- deactivate temporary customer account from Customer Management page (bonus functionnality). The user will be blocked if the option in the customer backend is set to no.&amp;#xD;
- The default template override some customer and checkout views to adapt display for login pages, checkout process and account edition in frontend. If you have a customized template, please check the layout file username.xml and compare with your template to use or adapt to your situation.&amp;#xD;
&amp;#xD;
Compatible Magento version &amp;gt;= 1.4.2 until 1.9.1</description>
   <license>OSL v3.0</license>
   <license_uri>http://www.opensource.org/licenses/osl-3.0.php</license_uri>
   <version>2.2.1</version>
   <stability>stable</stability>
   <notes>e694fcb Add custom input validation
85a0f51 Update translations
1ca6441 Update Copyright
799fc1b [FIX] prevent to save username when it&apos;s not allowed from configuration
55ab34e make the module compatible with MAgento 1.8, change copyright, move column logic for customer grid into observer
6c49218 Merge pull request #7 from gdhnz/master
bad7445 Add permission &quot;allow everything&quot; to adminhtml.xml to resolve admin 404 for the extension config screen under CE 1.8
fa712c7 Code factoring
6c603d8 fix comment typo
5f5fe14 change to version 2.0.7
41e58bb fix bad condition test in case of not found $customerId in Form.php. Use case, checkout process with already logged in customer.
b8e71c7 add submodule MageTrashApp
757a3e2 Update README.md
48244a4 add version 2.0.6
e9453ff generate correctly username for old customers while installing the module
f422067 Fix to the controller forgotPassword
fd71c66 change version to 2.0.5
67bf362 cleanup some test
adc2bb5 add fix when customer information are saved from backend, add observer fix for collection (do not know yet if it resolved hte problem of a user who contacted me about grid 
1c0c07f change version number
4ab072f fix bad merging
cd2bb86 Update README.md
fa3f821 Update composer.json
d10136e add dependency suggestion
ff053ba remove todo task
b300aa0 Fix a problem with sql data install with empty select query
5b179b5 add uninstall process for module MageTrashApp
ce428e9 add composer.json
d93cc55 merge observer
29d4c21 add condition to test if attribute username model exists before to save the config
14acf45 Update README.md
21f72b7 add missing column for sales_flat_order table
612052d improve checkout process as a guest (no complain that username is a required field when you are a guest), fix issue with install data script
aafb0be split template depending on the magento version, add missing template for use cases using persisten customer feature
ce9245b Fix or improve form model while saving new customer data
42444f3 Improve test if shop owner change the account sharing options
4d10edb Improve Username Module: setup is now completly rewritten for Magento 1.7, add username for forgotten password, allow now to disable the feature from configuration page, ch
c6b7250 add customer ID fix depending on the context
788e656 add optionable strtolower username
49cb18d add optionable strtolower username
dff09e0 Add modman and instruction to use it
2d6b6c8 Merge pull request #1 from clst/master
1d143e9 fix: weird quote characters in german language file
9cbf4a2 add: can now update is_active for existing customers
dfa9cc6 Fix some bug and add a way to import is_active attribute
60c7143 Update README.md
24afad2 add gitignore and license files
</notes>
   <authors>
      <name>
         <name>diglin</name>
      </name>
      <user>
         <user>diglin</user>
      </user>
      <email>
         <email>sly@diglin.com</email>
      </email>
   </authors>
   <depends_php_min>5.2.9</depends_php_min>
   <depends_php_max>6.0.0</depends_php_max>
   <depends>
      <package>
         <name>
            <name/>
         </name>
         <channel>
            <channel/>
         </channel>
         <min>
            <min/>
         </min>
         <max>
            <max/>
         </max>
         <files>
            <files>    </files>
         </files>
      </package>
      <extension>
         <name>
            <name>Core</name>
         </name>
         <min>
            <min/>
         </min>
         <max>
            <max/>
         </max>
      </extension>
   </depends>
   <contents>
      <target>
         <target>magelocal</target>
         <target>magecommunity</target>
         <target>mageetc</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
      </target>
      <path>
         <path/>
         <path>Diglin/Username</path>
         <path>modules/Diglin_Username.xml</path>
         <path>adminhtml/default/default/template/username</path>
         <path>frontend/base/default/layout/username.xml</path>
         <path>frontend/base/default/template/username</path>
         <path>de_DE/Diglin_Username.csv</path>
         <path>en_GB/Diglin_Username.csv</path>
         <path>en_US/Diglin_Username.csv</path>
         <path>fr_FR/Diglin_Username.csv</path>
      </path>
      <type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
      </type>
      <include>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
      </include>
      <ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
      </ignore>
   </contents>
</_>
